{
    "id": "f78f94c307c3487bb6e74d37dc2d3706",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His ………………… led to his fall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "proud",
                "pride"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "990c209f5b2744109963329e922ac459"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are waiting for the …………………. of the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "confirm",
                "conform",
                "confirmation"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f6dbb9f3de384cd3a3c660d680e672a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Failure is the stepping stone to …………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "success",
                "succession"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a8982a065889433195c52bfb316d2917"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is an ……………….  young man driven by his desire to change the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ambition",
                "ambiguous",
                "ambitious"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b5c354465d1943c8ac4097c609d75b7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "One should be satisfied with one’s …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "accomply",
                "accomplish",
                "accomplishments"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "23c85a55973a4e7b9b862431cb631c56"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ………………….. to learn English helped him in his later life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "determine",
                "determination",
                "determinant"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "706d3fab643044ee8a9ca6f3ced65d02"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you follow my advice, you will ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "success",
                "successful",
                "succeed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "504b5000139b495598b77b62463193e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "His father has given him his …………………. to go abroad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "permit",
                "permission",
                "permissible"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fe613bf1455546868edd0cd67acd47d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ……………….. is contagious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enthuse",
                "enthusiasm",
                "enthusiastic"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "510507df17b241f8b4676aad95e53f70"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is very ………………… about his new project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enthuse",
                "enthusiastic",
                "enthusiasm"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0d6a195c8e0c42b08add14c63313f7a3"
        }
    ]
}